Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Walter Tandy Murch papers
- Art Work, 1891-1967, Series 7:; (Box 7, 10, OV 11; 33 folders)
  - Pencil Drawings, 1934-1946, undated, (4 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10 and OV 11) (Box 7, Folder 46-49)
  - Ink Drawings, 1940-1967, undated, (2 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 7, Folder 50-51)
  - Charcoal Drawings, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Mixed Media Drawings, 1953, undated, (3 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 7, Folder 53-55)
  - Watercolor Sketches, undated, (5 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 7, Folder 56-60)
  - Watercolor Sketches for a Mural, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Designs for Woodcuts, 1929, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Woodcuts with Original Drawings, undated, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 63-64)
  - Woodcuts, 1935, undated, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 65-66)
  - Sketches for "Novel in Woodcut," undated, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 67-69)
  - Oil Portrait of a Woman, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Mock-Up of Book Notes on the Hound of Heaven, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Art Work by Others: Painting by L. M., undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Art Work by Others: Sketchbook by Walter Scott Murch, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Children's Art Work, 1945-1964, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Oversized Pencil Drawings, undated, (from Box 7, Folder 47) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Pencil Drawings, 1932, undated, (from Box 7, Folder 47) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Ink Drawings, undated, (from Box 7, Folders 50-51) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Mixed Media Drawings, undated, (from Box 7, Folder 54) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Watercolor Sketches, undated, (from Box 7, Folder 56) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Pencil Drawing, undated, (from Box 7, Folder 47) (Box 11)
- Printed Material, 1926-1968, Series 8:; (Box 7-8, 10, OV 11; 50 folders)
  Printed material consists of clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs for Murch and others, press releases, prospectuses, reproductions of art work and book jackets designed by Murch, programs, brochures, a book about Pierre Bonnard, and miscellaneous printed material.
  - Clippings, 1926-1966, undated, (13 folders) (Box 7, Folder 75-87)
  - Clippings, 1967-1968, (5 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
  - Hand-Made Collegiate School Magazine The New Thinker, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1929-1967, undated, (11 folders) (Box 8, Folder 7-17)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs for Others, 1931, 1964-1967, undated, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
  - Press Releases, 1952-1966 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Prospectuses, 1931-1967, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Reproductions of Art Work by Murch, 1950-1962, undated, (6 folders)(Oversized Material Housed in Box 10 and OV 11) (Box 8, Folder 23-28)
  - Programs, 1943-1967, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Book Jackets Designed by Murch, 1930-1945, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 31-32)
  - Book Bonnard from Les ?ditions Braun and Cie, Paris, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Reproduction of a Book of Business and Trade Cuts (Images), undated, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - World War II Ration Books, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1947-1964, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in OV 11) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Oversized Reproductions of Art Work by Murch, 1950-1961, undated, (from Box 8, Folders 23 and 25-28) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Program, 1947, (from Box 8, Folder 29) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Reproductions of Art Work by Murch, 1953, (from Box 8, Folder 25) (Box 11)
  - Oversized Poster Concerning Ad Reinhardt, 1955, (from Box 8, Folder 37) (Box 11)
  - Oversized Sample of Wallpaper, undated, (from Box 8, Folder 37) (Box 11)
- Photographs, Title1908-1967, Series 9:; (Box 9-10; 41 folders)
  Photographs are of Murch, family members, travel destinations, miscellaneous buildings, Murch's studio, Murch with colleagues, exhibition installations, subjects for art work, and of art work by Murch and others.
  - Murch, 1917-1961, undated, (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
  - Family Members, 1908-1966, undated, (7 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 5-11)
  - Wedding Day of Walter Scott Murch and Muriel A. Slater, 1965, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 12-14)
  - Travel Photographs, 1936, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Buildings, 1937-1965, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Murch's Studio, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Murch with Art Juries, 1967, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Exhibition Installations, 1947-1948, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Subjects for Art Work: Clocks, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Subjects for Art Work: Early Computers, 1953, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Subjects for Art Work: Unidentified Mechanical Device, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Subjects for Art Work: Violin Maker, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects for Art Work, 1953, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Drawings by Murch, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Paintings by Murch, undated, (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 26-29)
  - Design for Stained Glass by Murch, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Commercial Art Work by Murch: Lord and Taylor Store, 1935, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Commercial Art Work by Murch: Miscellaneous Stores, 1941-1947, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Commercial Art Work by Murch: Miscellaneous Murals, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Commercial Art Work by Murch: Miscellaneous Advertisements, 1951, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Paintings by Others, undated, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 35-37)
  - Photographs of Sculpture by Others, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Drawings by Others, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Art Work by Others, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Oversized Photograph of Frank Murch, 1932, (from Box 9, Folder 6) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of a Mural, undated, (from Box 9, Folder 33) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Advertisements, 1951, undated, (from Box 9, Folder 34) (Box 10, Folder 6)